Connor Kai-Ho Lee

connor.lee@yale.edu 626-377-5522

OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated college student at Yale university interested in gaining experience in social-robotics. Through my organization and communication skills, I can solve problems both independently and collaboratively. I have demonstrated reliable service and worthy contribution to the development of quality products and projects during my previous internships, and I would be a beneficial asset to your team.

EDUCATION

Yale University, New Haven, CT

2019 - Present

Bachelor of Arts in Cognitive Science (2024)

- Cognitive Science Coursework: Thinking, Mental Lives of Babies and Animals, Mystery of Sleep, Intro to Cognitive Science
- CS Coursework: Intro to Information Systems, Computer Science & the Modern Intellectual Agenda

Loyola High School, Los Angeles, CA

2015 - 2019

Highschool Diploma

- Cum Laude
- Loyola Men's Varsity Swim Team Captain (2018-2019)
- USA Swimming Scholastic All-American (2016-2019)

TECHNICAL PROFILE

Programming:

• Python (2 years); HTML (1 year); CSS (1 year); MATLAB (<1 year); Swift (<1 year)

Platforms & Systems:

Windows; Mac OSX; Linux

Other:

Microsoft Office Suite; Google's G Suite Adobe Photoshop

WORK EXPERIENCE

Yale Interactive Machines Group, New Haven, CT

Research Assistant

August 2021 - Present

· Machine-learning data analyst

Schulte Research, Austin, TX (remote)

Research Intern

January 2021 - April 2021

- Spearheaded research on the new wave of PropTech startup companies by exploring venture capital firms' portfolios
- Acknowledged in Paul Schulte's book The Digital Transformation of Property in Greater China: Finance, 5G, Al, and Blockchain
- Discussed with teammates about the viability of 25+ PropTech companies in terms of business objective, user platform, and practicality of technological tools
- Prepared a 50-page PowerPoint highlighting eight potentially successful companies' growth, business models, and market strategies

LinQuest Corp., Los Angeles, CA (remote)

Finance Intern

- Created 10+ spreadsheets daily for program managers to evaluate budget allocations and analyze costs for upcoming projects
- Used Salesforce to organize completed proposals and company expenditures for accessibility, visibility, and auditing
- Managed weekly COVID-19 business interruption charge reports during the coronavirus pandemic ensuring employee efficiency

Yale University, New Haven, CT

Men's Swimming and Diving Member

Aug 2019 - Present

- 20 hours a week of training
- 2020 US Olympic Trials qualifier
- 2020 Ivy League Champion
- · School record holder in 100 Butterfly and 50 Butterfly

Organizations

Yale Undergraduate Aerospace Association

2021

• Worked with a team of fellow Yale students to engineer a 2-stage rocket that reached an altitude of 30,000 feet

Volunteering

Loyola Senior Service Project, Los Angeles, CA

2019

Aided teachers at an impoverished LA county elementary school by tutoring students in reading and writing

Los Angeles Food Bank, Los Angeles, CA

2016

Packaged and sorted food items for distribution among underprivileged citizens living in LA County

2016

Built a 2-story house and privy for a homeless woman with a team of 10 classmates and their fathers

LANGUAGES

Baja Build, Tijuana, MX

English (Native)

Star Wars, Skateboarding, Movies, Anime, Music, Traveling, LEGO

U.S. Citizen

Connor Kai-Ho Lee

connor.lee@yale.edu 626-377-5522

REFERENCES

Jim Henry, Robert J.H. Kiphuth Head Coach @ Yale Swimming & Diving james.henry@yale.edu

Paul Schulte, Founder @ Schulte Research paul@schulte-research.co

U.S. Citizen